# DAMAR GALIH

♦ YOGYAKARTA, INDONESIA 

• 082223223166

# DETAILS

Yogyakarta Indonesia 082223223166 dgdarma6@gmail.com

#### SKILLS

Fast Learner

Leadership

Communication

Computer Skills

Leadership and Teamwork

**Creative Thinking** 

Web Developer

# HOBBIES

Menulis Program, Bermain Musik, Dll

# PROFILE

I am a human who is interested in the world of technology, especially in the field of development and manufacture. I try to continue to broaden my knowledge and gain new experiences. However, on the other hand, my love of philosophy gives me expertise in understanding identity and the meaning of life. The combination of technological expertise and philosophical understanding is able to create a unique perspective and produce interesting works. That's me, thank you.

# EDUCATION

SD/MI, MI Ma'arif Kalisana, Kebumen 2010 — 2016

2010 2010

SMP, SMP N1 Karangsambung, Kebumen

2016 - 2019

SMA N1 Karangsambung, Kebumen

2019 - 2022

Universitas Amikom Yogyakarta, Yogyakarta

2022 - Present

# EXPERIENCE

Leader at Scouts of SMP N 1 Karangsambung, Kebumen

2018 - 2019

Religious Field at OSIS SMP N1 Karangsambung, Kebumen

2018 - 2019

Leader at Scouts of SMA N 1 Karangsambung, Kebumen

2021 - 2022

Religious Field at SMA N1 Karangsambung

2021 - 2022

Member at Amicom Computer Club, Yogyakarta

2022 - Present

# COURSES

Full Stack Developer, Codepolitan

2022 — Present

Front-end, Dicoding Indonesia

2022 - 2023

# REFERENCES

References available upon request